sharenxs.com 2018-01-15

# Privacy Policy | ShareNXS

ShareNXS ("ShareNXS", "we," "us," "our") collects information from you when you register on our site or place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience 

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

* To improve our website 

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

* To improve customer service 

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

* To process transactions 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

* To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
* To send newsletters

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information.

All supplied credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime either through the website via editing their account information or by contact us using our support page available at http://www.sharenxs.com/content/support

#### Visitors Under Age 13

Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. In case you are under age 13, please do not attempt to provide any personal information about yourself to us. We will delete any personal information as soon as possible once we learn that this information is from any person under age 13.

#### CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.sharenxs.com/content/tos

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on **August 22, 2013**

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at the webpage available at http://www.sharenxs.com/content/support to contact us.

#### Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives: 

  * California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Privacy Alliance
  * Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
